ztelligence.com 2000-12-02

# zTelligence - Privacy

zTelligence is committed to its policy of protecting the privacy and confidential information of Members, who register to build and deploy surveys and who from time to time might purchase services offered by zTelligence, and Panelists, who register to respond to and answer surveys.

**What personally identifiable information does zTelligence collect and what does zTelligence do with it?**

Upon registration, Members provide us with personal information such as their name, address and email address. We use this information to establish individual accounts and lockers, protected by a password the Member selects. We ask for some additional demographic information from our Panelists to determine their eligibility to participate in surveys requiring Panelists who meet a specific demographic profile.

With respect to both Members and Panelists, zTelligence uses the email address supplied in the registration process to confirm registration, and to send notices and updates to you concerning the services and the site. We will also add you to zTelligence's mailing list if you requested that during registration.

zTelligence also uses "cookies," or small pieces of information that we store on users' computers, to recognize returning users and to monitor traffic through the site. This information helps us to make the site better and more user-friendly. We use either cookies or weblogs to collect users IP addresses and log-in times that are identified by individual user. Finally, we collect the surveys and survey results that you have either deployed or participated in.

NOTE TO PARENTS AND MINORS: We do not want to collect any personal information whatsoever of minors-in fact, we ask that minors do not submit any information about themselves and that they not use this Site. Anyone using this Site or the Services warrants and promises that they are 18 years of age or older.

**Does zTelligence Disclose My Personally Identifiable Information to Other Members?**

No. All zTelligence does is send surveys to Panelists on behalf of Members. zTelligence sends these surveys without disclosing any personally identifiable information on its Panelists. Demographic information on Panelists that a Member may require is disclosed only in aggregate form.

Panelists should be aware, however, that in responding to surveys or survey invitations that they may be disclosing their own personally identifiable information to Members. The security and privacy protections in place on this Site and through the Service do not cover this type of transfer or disclosure of personal information. Panelists responding to surveys or survey invitations are solely responsible for the content of their responses.

**To Whom Do We Disclose Personal Information?**

As a rule, we will not sell, distribute, publish or otherwise disclose your personally identifying information without your express permission through an email authorization. However, if we believe you have breached the Terms of Agreement, especially with regard to transmitting, publishing or distributing pornographic, obscene, offensive, threatening, harassing, libelous, hate-oriented, harmful, defamatory, racist, illegal or otherwise objectionable materials or content, we will report such conduct to the appropriate authorities and turn over any and all information, including personal identifying information, to appropriate persons or entities. We will also comply with any laws or legal process that may require disclosure of personal identifying information.

**How does zTelligence store my Personally Identifiable Information?**

zTelligence stores personal information of Members and Panelists in secure databases protected by passwords as well as database and network firewalls to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of personal information. While no security systems are infallible, MarketTools (zTelligence's parent company) will prosecute any unauthorized access to secured information to the fullest extent of the law. zTelligence periodically reviews and updates security measures to insure the best possible protections for the membership.

**Can I Delete Personally Identifiable Information on the site?**

You can notify us at any time to remove your registration information from our database by emailing us at support@markettools.com. If you do that, we will not keep any personally identifiable records concerning you unless required to do so by law. However, if you make this request you will be unable to access or use the account you previously created and its associated content without going through the registration process again. In addition, zTelligence cannot retrieve any personally identifiable information Panelists may have disclosed to Members in responding to surveys.

**Does zTelligence Collect or Disclose Information (email addresses, names) That I Supply in Order to Send Surveys?**

No. When you enter email information for your survey recipients or establish email lists in your personal Email List Manager, that information remains untouched and private in your personal locker. Your password protects that information. zTelligence never discloses that information and if it ever wanted to, zTelligence would get express approval from you first. However, if you have breached the Terms of Agreement, zTelligence will report such conduct to the appropriate authorities and turn over any and all information, including personally identifying information, to appropriate persons or entities.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

If zTelligence wishes to change this policy, it will publish changes on this Web site before those changes will take effect. zTelligence will also notify users of changes to this policy via electronic mail. As always, if you do not agree with zTelligence's privacy policy, you have the option of requesting that we delete your personally identifiable information from the site. For more information policies, see our terms of agreement.
